

Vitalii Bondarchuk

Junior Front-end & React.js Developer

- +38 096 266 90 70
- S vit.bondarchuk
- @ vit.bondarchuk@gmail.com
- in www.linkedin.com/in/vitalii-bondarchuk/
- Yviv, Ukraine

SUMMARY

I'm a front-end developer with multitasking skills. Supportive and enthusiastic team player to streamlining processes and efficiently resolving project issues on the future team. Friendly, positive, highly motivated person. Attentive to details. More than five years of working experience in IT as a UI/UX designer.

SKILLS

HTML5 **JavaScript** UX / UI CSS3 React.is Figma SCSS / Sass Redux Sketch NPM / Yarn Git / GitHub Photoshop Webpack AJAX Illustrator

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

Front-end & UI/UX 12/2018 – present time

- coding parts of sites in JavaScript;
- layouting: HTML/CSS, preprocessors;
- verifying and modifying UI designs.

Luxoft, IT-company

- UI/UX & Graphic Designer 07/2015 - 11/2018
- support designs for Luxoft's products;
- presentations/banners/prints;
- making video tutorials for software.

FCB, Advertising Agency **DTP-Designer**

03/2008 - 06/2015

- working with whole range of prints;
- color correction and profiling;
- 3D-molding, stereo-vario.

KP Media, Publishing Holding

Technical Designer 10/2004 - 03/2008

- scanning, retouching, collaging;
- color correction;
- prepress.

GITHUB & DESIGN PORTFOLIO

https://github.com/vitbon

Be https://www.behance.net/vitbon

LANGUAGES







EDUCATION

Cursor Education

Advanced Front-end Course 07/2020 - 10/2020

- HTML5 / CSS3:
- JavaScript (ES5 / ES6+);
- React.js.

Vinnitsa Technical University

Faculty of Computer Systems 09/1996 - 06/2001

- C, Basic, Assembler coding;
- programming measuring devices;
- honors degree.

Kyiv Evangel University

Faculty of Christian Education 09/2014 - 08/2018

• branch of Global University (USA);

- modern western programm;
- American lecturers.

CERTIFICATIONS

Cursor Education

- Advanced Front-end
- 07/2020 10/2020
- modern technologies;
- many practical tasks;
- excellent final result.

Luxoft

- British programm; • upper intermediate level;
- **English Courses** 10/2016 - 10/2018
- native speaker.

POST SCRIPTUM

Does your company need a proactive specialist with a desire to develop and move your business forward? Contact me, I'm that person! ©

INTERESTS









Photo/Video Design

Literature

History